Rami Hamdi

Date of birth: 1991 | **Nationality:** Tunisian | **Gender:** Male | **Phone number:** (+216) 96784599 (Mobile) |

Email address: rami.hamdi.2023@gmail.com | Website: https://simapps.github.io/Rami Hamdi | LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/rami-hamdi-57b371149/ Address: Tinja, Bizerte, Tunisia (Home)

ABOUT ME

With seven years of experience as a Navy Special Force officer, I possess a unique set of skills that make me a versatile and highly competent individual, capable of tackling a wide range of challenges. I am passionate about mobile development and I am constantly expanding my knowledge of new technologies and techniques.

WORK EXPERIENCE

07/2022 - CURRENT Tunisia

ANDROID DEVELOPER (FREELANCE) ALL SOFT MULTIMEDIA

- 1. Mainely worked on ProCaisse Mobility and ProInventory Mobile:
 - Reduced app crashes by 50% by implementing a new testing framework and improving code quality.
 - Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design and implement new features that enhanced user experience and addressed key business needs.
- 2. Developed an app that combines both Mobility and inventory and migrated both apps to Kotlin and letpack Compose:
 - Decreased loading data time by 60% by implementing parallel requests.
 - Improved the overall performance by 40% compared to legacy apps.
 - Improved user experience.

Technologies: Java, Kotlin, Dagger Hilt, Room, JetPack, Material3, Ktor, RESTful APIs, Git

Website https://www.asm-tunisie.com/

10/2023 - 02/2024 Tunisia

MOBILE DEVELOPER FLUTTER (FREELANCE) DND SERV

- 1. Develop a school management application for over 1000 users.
- 2. Develop a delivery app.

Technologies: Flutter, Floor, providers, Riverpod, RESTful APIs, Git, Firebase

Website https://dndserv.com/

2018 - CURRENT Tunisia

PERSONAL PROJECTS ANDROID DEVELOPER

Project Name: Prix en Tunisie

Compare product prices between different supermarkets, create a shopping list, and save FidCard Barecode.

Project Name: Radio FM AM

Play 30 000 Radio stations, record radio shows, work as an alarm, and synchronize favorite stations between different devices.

Technologies:

Firebase, Kotlin, Dagger Hilt, Databinding, MVVM, LiveData, Navigation, Single Activity approach, JetPack, ROOM, RESTful APIs, Gradle

2016 - 2023 Tunisia

NAVY OFFICER MINISTRY OF DEFENSE TUNISIA

Responsible for the accountability, mission readiness, and professional development of all personnel within my company.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2018 - 2021 Tunis, Tunisia

MASTER IN INTEGRATED MANAGEMENT QUALITY SAFETY ENVIRONMENT Tunis Higher Institute of Management

Thesis Migration from ohsas 18001 to ISO 45001

23/09/2019 - 14/05/2020 Menzel Bourguiba, Tunisia

CAPTAINS COURSES School of specialties and application

2015 - 2016 CasaBlanca, Morocco

THE NAVY SCHOOL OF APPLICATION Royal Naval School

2013 – 2015 Foundok Jdid, Tunisia

WEAPONS SCIENCE ENGINEER Military Academy

Thesis Design and construction of a system fixing weapons on shooting carriage

2010 - 2012 Sousse, Tunisia

BACHELOR LICENSE IN PHYSICS-CHEMISTRY Tunisia Prepartory School for the Military Academis

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ARABIC**

Other language(s): FRENCH | ENGLISH

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B